let's look at the solution to our LRU
quiz we had this situation in the cache
and these counters before these accesses
and now we're performing accesses to a B
a D and K a is the most recently used
block weary access it none of the
counters change we access B B's counter
becomes 7 from 3 that means that all the
counters above 3 will be decremented 2
stays the same one stays the same and
zero stays the same so these are the new
counters after B is accessed next we
access a again this counter becomes 7
all of the counters above 6 are
decremented so this is really the only
change now D is accessed this counter
becomes 7 those above 5 are decremented
the remaining ones stay the same all of
these have been hit so far so nothing
has changed in the cache we still have
exactly the same stuff there the only
change will be when we access K which is
a Miss so now we need to choose who goes
out and the one that goes out is the one
whose counter is zero so H is replaced
by K the other blocks remain the same as
they were and this is the final answer
for this quiz